So I don't make a habit of sharing text on here, but I had to make an exception.
So something I take Dolores Umbridge with is when like white people who have been welcomed into like
black groups and spaces and culture, like don't respect that. So when I saw Michael Rappaport,
like consistently espousing Zionist rhetoric, and I've heard so many stories of him coming at
black women on this internet in a wild way. I just was like, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't.
He's somebody that I've definitely considered an acquaintance. We've had a laugh together,
we're comics, et cetera, but enough was enough. So I texted him and I said, I'm genuinely shocked
that the peace OS racist Zionist you have revealed yourself to be. I have defended you so many times
in the past and continue to be disgusted that I ever use my time and my breath to support such a
despicable human being. Keep black people out your fucking mouth. And I meant that. His response was
interesting. He said, who gives a shit what the fuck you're Jewish hating, desperate, lonely,
goofy, big gum. That was the wrong use of your Jewish hating where all was with this small teeth
ass ever thinks could give a fuck what you defend, think or do get a man, have some kids, make a
turkey, do one set without mentioning white people. I would love for white people to not give me a
reason to mention them. Hit up a dentist, do it all. And the fuck else. Okay. Here's the thing.
You spent all this time around black folks and you still don't know how to roast somebody.
What a waste of an invite to the picnic. How y'all clap back off beat.